Why have you let him come back as S.I.O.?
你为什么让他回来做高级调查官
He saved your life.
他救过你的命
He's a hero to the guys out there.
对办公室外的同事们 他是英雄
But we know he's rotten.
但是我们知道他完全堕落了
Knowing's not the same as proving.
知道和能证明是两码事
It's about time you pay a visit to Lily-Anne Lau.
是时候去走访Lily-Anne Lau了
Lily-Anne Lau?
Lily-Anne Lau是谁
We need a physical record of what went on between Harry and her father.
我们需要一个事物记录 证明Harry和他父亲之间发生的事情
I keep thinking I'm seeing Ben everywhere.
我不停地在想我到处都在看到Ben
Is that weird?
是不是很怪异
No.
不
I've tipped off a mate of mine in Vice about the Green Dragon roulette tables.
What?
什么
I'm not letting Lily-Anne Lau just get away with this.
我不会让Lily-Anne Lau逃脱的
Hello. I'm Brett Stonewood. Kate Olsen's boss.
你们好 我是Brett Stonewood  Kate Olsen的上司
In the past few months, Olsen has just been working on one case.
过去几个月里 Olsen一直在负责一个案子
If I'm honest, we've had concerns about Kate for quite a while now.
我们担心Kate已经有一阵子了 如果我说的是实话
What do you mean?
什么意思
Kate's behaviour has been...
Kate的行为
erratic.
很不稳定
This case started to consume her.
这个案子消耗了她很多精力
She started chasing down obscure foreign leads,
sometimes punching in a week later.
So the fact she's missing doesn't surprise or worry you?
那么 她的失踪并没有让你吃惊或者担心
I didn't say that.
我可没那么说
Who's that? I know him.
那是谁  我认识他
Vincent Lermontov.
是Vincent Lermontov
Yes. He's the former CEO of the company Kate was investigating.
没错 他是Kate正在调查那家公司的前任首席执行官
He died... two weeks ago?
他死了  两周前死的
By jumping off the needle building.
跳楼了
Yes.
没错
Why was she investigating in him?
Kate为什么调查这个人
Vincent Lermontov was a gold bullion dealer.
Vincent Lermontov原是个金牌黄金交易商
He bought and sold huge quantities of gold.
他倒手买卖天量黄金
Kate became convinced that... he was too good at it.
Kate确信 他太过擅长这项交易了
But I'm guessing she didn't convince you.
不过我猜她并没有说服你相信
We work on evidence... And...
我们是看证据的  可是
there was none.
并没有证据
What does that mean "too good at it"?
你说的“太过擅长” 是什么意思
Kate thought that Lermontov's results were beyond all probability.
Kate认为Lermontov逢交易必赚钱这个结果 超出了所有可能
That basically, Vincent Lermontov was just... too...
主要就是  Vincent Lermontov 太
Too lucky.
太走运
Who runs Lermontov's International now?
现在谁执掌Lermontov国际
His son, Paul Lermontov.
Paul Lermontov 他的儿子
Kate had an appointment to meet him, last night.
昨晚 Kate约了Paul Lermontov
Just before she went missing.
恰好在她失踪前
I only found out about it today.
我今天才发现
She never told me about it.
她从来没告诉过我
Sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry,  I have to go to this meeting but...
不好意思 我得去开会了 但是
you will keep me up to date, please?
请两位告知我最新消息
OK?
好吗
Sir, ma'am.
两位长官
This is the flat of someone with no interest apart from their work.
这就是那个除了工作 对什么都没兴趣的家伙的公司
One to use, one to wash.
一个用的 一个洗的
Anything?
发现什么了
- She has type-I diabetes.  - What?
- 她患有I型糖尿病  - 什么
This is an emergency Click and go kit.
这个是紧急注射工具
She has to maintain her glucose level with regular carbs
她得保持葡萄糖水平在常规水平
or eat some sugar or she'll get woozy and loose consciousness.
或者吃糖 否则她会出现头晕并且失去知觉
What happens if she doesn't have it?
如果没有及时补充她会怎么样
She's in trouble.
她有麻烦了
- Fentanyl.  - Yeah!
- 芬太奴 强效止痛剂  - 没错
Forensics found tiny traces all over on Olsen's desk.
Forensics在Olsen桌上发现遍布的痕迹
It's used as an anaesthetic, you can get it on the black market.
这是作为麻醉剂使用的 黑市上都能买到
Someone knocked her out.
有人把她打晕了
We went to Olsen's flat.  We found syringes and insulin.
我们去了Olsen的住所 发现了注射器和胰岛素
We think she's prone to hypoglycaemia.
我们认为她有低血糖的倾向
If Olsen's glucose level drops when she's under,
如果Olsen的血糖水平降下来
the kidnappers will have to act fast.
绑架者会加快行动的
Maybe that's the point.
这个貌似说到点上了
The perfect murder is a murder we can't prove.
完美的谋杀就是无法被人证明的谋杀
All they would have to do is deny her any food, sugar and... just wait!
他们所做的就是让她吃不到食物 摄取不到糖分  就让她干等着
If that happened, it'd be very hard to prove she didn't die naturally.
如果是这样 那就很难证明她不是非正常死亡了
Can I get on with my job, please?
我能继续我的工作了吗
I thought you did this for fun though!
我觉得你干这份工纯属寻开心
Listen, will you try to make sense of all the charts and figures in Olsen's files?
听着 你能把Olsen档案里的图标和数字理出头绪来吗
I'll be next door if you need me.
我就在隔壁 需要时叫我
Jesus!
我的天
24th of April 1986...
1986年4月24日
Harry?
是Harry吗
Get on line. I need you to look at something.
快点上网 我需要你看点东西
You're unbelievable.
你真是难以置信
Aaahhh!
啊
Mum!
妈妈
That looks very very similar.
这个看起来很相似
Who's this dude?
这家伙是谁
He's a dead dude, Vincent Lermontov. He's a gold bullion dealer billionaire.
他是个死人 叫Vincent Lermontov 黄金交易界的亿万富豪
Look at the dragons.
瞧他手上那条龙
And the extra long yang line. It's definitely the same Ming Yun bracelet.
看那条额外长的阳线 这肯定是同一个命运手环
You know what, Harry? Now that I'm awake,
Harry 知道吗 我现在彻底清醒了
I'm 100% sure. It's definitely the same bracelet.
我完全确定 这是同一个手环
Yeah. I thought so.
我想是的
Hold.
等一下
I gotta go. Anna's on the other line.  Bye.
我得挂了 Anna在另一条线上等着呢  再见
Anna?
Anna
What have you got?
发现什么了
You can partially disable the F.R.S.A. building from the cable room in the basement,
在地下室的电报间动手 能让F.R.S.A.大楼陷入部分瘫痪
but it's not easily done.
但这可没那么容易办到
Check the CCTV on the roads out the Isle of Dogs.
检查犬岛外道路上的中央监控
If we're lucky, we might isolate the vehicle in the same time frame.
如果走运 我们可能把交通工具隔离到同一个时间框
Copy that.
收到
There's a young woman. She says she urgently needs to speak to Harry?
门外来了个年轻女子 她说她有紧急的事情要找Harry
Oh, thanks for coming by! She's really worked up.
多谢你赶来 她真是歇斯底里了
What the hell happened?
究竟发生什么事情了
She says she saw someone in the street.
她说她看到街上有个人
I... I don't know if she's lying...
我  我都不知道她是不是在说谎
Daddy! Daddy!
爸爸 爸爸
I saw a scary man looking at me!
我看见一个可怕的人 他盯着我看
So I hear! Alright! It's alright.
我听到了 没事了 没事了
Where's Harry?
Harry去哪里了
You've just missed him.
你刚好和他错过
When will he be back?
他什么时候回来
I'm sure he won't be long.
不会太久
I work with him.
我是他同事
So, hum... Why don't we start with your name?
那么 先说说你的名字吧
Eve.
我叫Eve
She fell asleep holding my hand.
她睡着了 还紧抓着我的手
She always used to do that, remember?
她过去总这样 还记得吗
You really don't have to stay.
你真的没必要留下
She won't wake up now.
她现在不会醒来的
Listen, I don't think it's safe for you to stay here.
听我说 我认为你在这里已经不安全了
I don't think she saw anyone, Harry. She just misses you.
Harry 我觉得她根本没看到任何人
I'll feel a lot better if I stay here. I'll sleep in the armchair.
我在这里会感觉好很多 我会睡在摇椅里的
Our hero.
你真是我们的英雄
How do you know Harry?
你怎么认识Harry的
I don't want to talk to you. I need to see Harry.
我不想和你讲 我要见Harry
Now.
现在
Why don't you tell me what the problem is, and I'll call him.
为什么不告诉我出了什么事 我会打电话给他
- You can't help me.  - Look, wait...
- 你没法儿帮我  - 等等
I can see you're in some kind of trouble.
我能看出你遇到麻烦了
Let go of me now.
现在放开我
Tell him he doesn't have to believe in me. He just has to believe in it.
转告Harry 他不需要相信我 他只要相信事实
Time's run out for me.
我没有多少时间了
Who is this Eve?
Eve是谁
No idea.
我没印象了
Well, she knew who you were.
她可是知道你是什么人呢
I think I figured out what made Olsen so obsessed with Vincent Lermontov.
我发现了Olsen如此沉迷于Vincent Lermontov的原因了
Oh yeah?
是吗
The price of gold always goes up when something very bad happens.
金价总是在不好的事情发生时上涨
Like Tottenham beating (Manchester) United?
比如托特纳姆热刺打曼联
No. Like wars, natural disasters, big stuff!
不 应该是战争 自然灾害 重大事件
These 3 dates are when Lermontov made his biggest investments in gold.
这三个日期正是Lermontov最大手笔黄金交易的日子
Read them out.
读出来
21st of December 1979
1979年12月21日
3 days before the Soviets invaded Afghanistan.
苏联入侵阿富汗前3天
24th of April 1986
1986年4月24日